https://www.buddhahouse.org/privacy-policy-disclaimer/

Buddha House
Affiliated with the Foundation for the Preservation of the Mahayana Tradition
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Buddha House . To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on these pages and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Buddha House website. On some pages, you can order services and make requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages may be any or all of the following: Name, Address, Phone Number, Email Address, IP Address
The credit and payment services we utilize to process your order have their own privacy statements which may be different from those found here at Buddha House . It is therefore recommended that you carefully read the privacy statements located on these other sites to help protect your privacy. We do not ask for nor keep credit card information.
How We Use Your Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties or collected in a database.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment to Your Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us at Buddha House . And for that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13. No part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.
Also, if we hear of, are informed of, or are witness to any illegal activity with, to, or directed at children, we will promptly report such parties to the proper authorities for prosecution.
DISCLAIMER
Website Disclaimer – Disclaimer of Endorsement:
Reference herein to any specific commercial products, process, or service by trade name, trademark, manufacturer, or otherwise, does not necessarily constitute or imply its endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by Buddha House. The views and opinions of authors expressed herein do not necessarily state or reflect those of Buddha House, and shall not be used for advertising or product endorsement purposes.
The appearance of external hyperlinks does not constitute endorsement by Buddha House of the linked web sites, or the information, products or services contained therein. For other than authorized activities, Buddha House does not exercise any editorial control over the information you may find at these locations. All links are provided with the intent of meeting the mission of Buddha House. Please let us know about existing external links which you believe are inappropriate and about specific additional external links which you believe ought to be included.
Disclaimer of Liability:
With respect to documents available from this server, neither Buddha House nor any of its employees, makes any warranty, express or implied, including the warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, or assumes any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, apparatus, product, or process disclosed, or represents that its use would not infringe privately owned rights.
Notice:
Information from this server resides on a computer system funded by Buddha House. The use of this system may be monitored for computer security purposes. Any unauthorized access to this system is prohibited and is subject to criminal and civil penalties under Federal Laws.
Reference from this web page or from any of the information services sponsored by Buddha House to any non-governmental entity, product, service or information does not constitute an endorsement or recommendation by Buddha House or any of its employees. We are not responsible for the content of any “off-site” web pages referenced from this server.
What is the Chenrezig Mantra?
The six syllables: om ma ni pad me hum, mean that you can transform your impure body, speech, and mind into the pure exalted body, speech, and mind of a Buddha.
The first known description of the mantra appears in the Karandavyuha Sutra (Buddha speaks Mahayana Sublime Treasure King Sutra), which is part of certain Mahayana canons. In this sutra, Shakyamuni Buddha states: This is the most beneficial mantra. Even I made this aspiration to all the million Buddhas and subsequently received this teaching from Buddha Amitabha.
Listen to the Chenrezig Mantra
Mercedes Bahleda
What’s On at Buddha House
Click the event title for full details
eNews SubscriptionClick Here to read latest news from FPMT
2021 Upcoming Events – Save the Dates
30 January 2021
“Fund Raising Fete”
Click Here – How you can Help
2 February 2021
Discovering Buddhism
Topic:   “How to Meditate”
Buddha House
496 Magill Road, Magill SA 5072.
Phone: 8333 2824
CLICK HERE TO CONTACT BUDDHA HOUSE
Privacy Policy/Disclaimer
Affiliated with the Foundation for the Preservation of the Mahayana Tradition (FPMT)
